Wow, would you look at that.
There are so many different rooms.
Don't get too excited.
Well,
love hotels aren't exactly professional.
I wasn't comfortable leaving her
at home while I'm away on business.
This room is gorgeous.
A cheap business hotel would've been fine,
but this is a little embarrassing.
Oh well!
This is the best.
I'm so happy to see you this pleased, Akane.
It definitely has nothing to do with being in a place
where she can easily pressure me into sex.
Hey, Akane?
Here it comes.
Listen, I have a really long meeting this evening,
so I need to go and prep for that, okay?
Understood.
I'll stay on standby so
I don't interfere with your work.
Wow, she can actually read the room.
All right, see you tomorrow.
Looking forward to it. See you then.
Wait, she seriously hasn't tried anything yet?
I was sure she'd pull something naughty on me,
but no, nothing.
Akane?
Yeah?!
Is your meeting over?
Yeah.
Here it is.
It's happening.
Well then, shall we go to bed?
Good night.
How the heck am I supposed to sleep?!
She really isn't going to make a move?!
I have an early start tomorrow,
so I should sleep, but...
Calm down.
Just calm down.
I can't take it anymore.
Huh? The TV?
That's so weird.
Why won't this stupid thing turn off?
That woman reminds me of you, Akane.
Huh? How so?
In the way she responds during sex.
Hey, Akane?
Would you like to recreate what they're doing?
Yes, I need it now.
You need what?
Go on, say it.
You know. Don't make me say it.
I wanna hear you beg, cutie.
Akane?
What would you like me to do?
Yes.
Please.
I need you to make me cum.
I can't say that, but...
Understood. Leave it to me.
Nadeshiko...
Thank you for the advice,
Mother.
I'm just glad I could help, Nadeshiko.
You were a huge help. By the way,
why did you only contact me?
Call me! I miss you~~
Love, Mama
Well, it's a bit too soon for me to meet your master.
I can't wait to introduce Akane to you, Mother.
Hmm. Is that so?
Fine.
Once she's officially registered
as your master, you can both come visit.
Really?
Then I'll work even harder
to complete her registration.